{
    "id": "527738a504314285b25b792bf1355c16",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ................................ his seventeenth year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81ca3c92cfe9446d8a97e12ce56c68da"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ...................................... eighteen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70560ef5353f4513bac395d4a6a05456"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... my opinion it is wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "With",
                "On"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "60b71cab3a46405aa26cb92268d30484"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our house is built .................................... bricks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1509caf4eb8f4b41994d43c5d42e87f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went ......................................... the building.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "behind",
                "back",
                "beneath"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f3ec411ea9be4f0e977793031048cded"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was prevented ................................... coming.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5090af1a090d4a6da99120b52903b424"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a match ..................................... Team A and Team B.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "among",
                "for",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "246ca3294f474c23a91b2f29f6d674aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a fight ................................... John and Peter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "between",
                "among",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a2508110feb414c893da58bec936110"
        },
        {
            "question": "The First World War was fought ................................. 1914 and",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a48876e2bb8848daa65ac3e6766bf573"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked ..................................... a rise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ae53464bd4b42148c40b307372dfce1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyday he walks ten miles ................................... foot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43cbe0767bcb4b0ab0ec49f3a7ddcfcc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I shall inform them ........................................ this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d034c7cb81cf4ce8b501c23218453eeb"
        }
    ]
}